{
	"questions": [
		{
			"question": "When was the last time you withdrew cash?",
			"answer": "Last Week"
		},
		{
			"question": "How much do you usually withdraw at an ATM?",
			"answer": "$50"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where did you most recently travel?",
			"answer": "Cleveland Ohio"
		},
		{
			"question": "How often did you dine out last week?",
			"answer": "Twice"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where was the last restaurant you ate at?",
			"answer": "Wendy's"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where is your go to place for grocery shopping?",
			"answer": "Whole Foods"
		},
		{
			"question": "When was the last time you went grocery shopping?",
			"answer": "January 25"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where did you get your car serviced?",
			"answer": "Pepboys"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where did you go gift shopping?",
			"answer": "Kards Unlimited"
		},
		{
			"question": "What charitable organizations have you recently donated to?",
			"answer": "United Way"
		},
		{
			"question": "What airline do you usually fly with?",
			"answer": "I never fly"
		},
		{
			"question": "Approximately how long have you been banking with PNC?",
			"answer": "About 4 years"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who was the last person you sent a Zella payment to?",
			"answer": "Luke"
		},
		{
			"question": "What are you saving up for right now?",
			"answer": "Vacation to Costa Rica"
		}
	]
}